<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" ml-update="aware" ml-stage="preload" ml-view="top">
  <channel>
    <title>heyjoeway</title>
    <link>http://sveltekit-prerender/feeds/main</link>
    <description>Cult of Dinonicest</description>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 23:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 23:28:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <docs>https://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>Custom</generator>
    <atom:link href="http://sveltekit-prerender/feeds/main/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <item>
      <title/>
      <link>http://sveltekit-prerender/feeds/main/021725_1131PM</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Okay so if this works I'm very close to actually starting to post. Testing edits&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 23:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>/feeds/main/021725_1131PM</guid>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title/>
      <link>http://sveltekit-prerender/feeds/main/022225_0448PM</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Alright, so I'm pretty much done developing v1 of this Twitter-clone... thing so I guess it's time to start using this. So, hi! By the end of this you'll probably realize that the character limit on posts is 1̵̨̡̭̜̣̝̖̗̩͈͚̻͚͍̿̄͆͂̀͝ͅ.̵̨̠͔̥͐̓̏͋͂8̷͓̈́̾̈́̀̂̾̾͑̓̀̿̚̕͠7̷̡̞͇̦̦̗̮̹̭̿͒̈́͑́̓͐͊́̉͑̉4̶̨̧̩̹̺͉̹̦̖̩̟̮̘̹͙̀͆̄̄̍̈́̉͠3̵̞̼̮̙̟̙͛̀̄̉͌̈͊͐̂̂̀͝e̴̢̡̳̰̭͚̖̦̺͔͗́̄4̷̡̩̺̞̟̘͈̼̫͎̭̝̘͍̘͎̊̒͝7̸̡̨̢̼̣͓͕̻̜͔̻͚͍̻̟͆̀̓͑̏͊̊͗̈̿̾̉̈́̾͆4̸̠̜̠͇̫̜̞̜͈͋͊̀̎͛̓8̴̧̛̺̘͖̜̖̻̰̹̜͎̠̭̱̾̀͐̈́͛̄̏̔͑̒͆͛́͐̚͠5̶̧̛͓̘̻̙̐̀̀̍̾̒̔̾͊́̚̚͝7̷̱͖̟̹͍̎̾̾̓͝4̸͔̬̜̠̜̪̳̹̋̌̕8̷̹̣̏̌͂̓̈́̽̏̈́́͊͠4̸̨̡͇͍͎͔͎͔̱̦̬͔̜͕̰̺̙͛͌̍̃̋̍́͊̔̂̑͗̃̚̚̚3̷̙̝̫͕͙̝̲̿̔͋͜͜ͅ9̶̧̮̟̺̠͚͍̯̮̟͍̳̣͇́̈́̿̉̽̉͋̄̓̀̊̂͆͊̕͜0̸̨̗̺̳͓̞̦̿̈̆̓͑̅̐͐̑͆̈́̎̒̕͝͝7̷̧͎̙̫͎̳͓̖̺̥̹͔̑̽͒4̴̧̨̨̜̺̘̺̣͖͇͓̝͇͕̮̳̄̋̆̏͛́̿̊̓̄̀͆͂͜͝͝&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Where the HELL did you go&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So IIRC I vanished off of Twitter at like, what, mid 2023? Late 2022? Deadass I can't even remember anymore. It was right before Musk bought it and god DAMN am I glad I jumped ship when I did. That being said my decision to get out wasn't really hinging on his ownership but that's a whole can of worms so I'll save that for later.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;tl;dr: I needed to lock the fuck in.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grad school was wrapping up (not the cleanest exit to say the least) and I had some VERY important decisions to make. Like for example, where my wife and I were gonna live! Permanently! We got an EXTREMELY good offer on a small house with a small catch. Just an, uh, teeny tiny itty bitty little thing. It wasn't finished. Not in the "needs renovation" sense, no, I mean the house got halfway through construction before some... circumstances... left it unfinished.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So I graduate and we're lucky enough that we're able to take a loan out to purchase the house and property on my parents' credit (since it's a construction loan and certain stipulations come with that and blah blah blblblbla), although we handle all expenses. And now I'm out of grad school and into NEET territory while I look for a job.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My god, if you're looking for a job right now: the current market with slam you with one of the most depressing, demoralizing, time-wasting experiences you will ever encounter. On one occasion, &lt;strong&gt;I received my rejection email before I got the confirmation that I applied&lt;/strong&gt;. The current narrative I see on Reddit right now that AI ATS filtering isn't a real thing is total astroturf BS. After like 2-3 months of searching though, I found a listing where HR actually DOES do their job, and that position I'm currently quite happy with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next year is basically spent funneling all of our extra money into building the house. Going by what my budgeting program says, to date we've spent about $20K. Which, for everything the house needed, is actually not that bad. Less than half of that spending came from a loan. I'll probably show off some of the place in the near future. Still not even close to "done", but really when is any house. The place was deemed livable towards the end of July and we &lt;em&gt;instantly&lt;/em&gt; moved in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The same week:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One of our cars completely shit the bed. We kinda saw it coming, the car was not exactly in the best state when we bought it. We were hoping we'd get another year out of it though. So there went another chunk of change and another loan to sell our souls with. The usual.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wife got new job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also brought to our new place my parents' cat that had really bonded with us. And about a month later, we adopted him a sister so he could have company. You &lt;strong&gt;will&lt;/strong&gt; be seeing them soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Uhhh okay what else. I've been doing a lot of homelab stuff. Still getting comfortable in our space, putting together rooms and desks and workbenches and stuff. I don't even know man. So much has happened that it is genuinely difficult to remember anything before last year. I'm hoping to break that mental barrier down and rediscover stuff that I used to enjoy. I've got so much other random shit to talk about but I think I'm running out of steam here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If anyone actually reads this PLEASE comment I need Internet Validation&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 23:28:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <guid>/feeds/main/022225_0448PM</guid>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>